Jaynish Buddhdev

Full-stack developer

India

🎧 jaynishb 🛅 jaynish-buddhdev 🚥 npx jaynishb

I'm a full stack developer based in India, having almost 7 years of expirence, working with small and big scale companies to help them to achieve their goals. I am ready to take on a challenge of a new level and add value to a project through my knowledge and expertise.

SKILLS -



WORK EXPERIENCE (3)

▼ Full stack developer | Atom Learning

Nov 2021 - Present

Q London, (UK) https://atomlearning.co.uk/

NodeJs ReactJs NestJs Jest Kafka AWS SQS Postgres

Atom learning is The all-in-one online learning platform for ages 7–11

- Acted as a full stack JavaScript engineer for the post atom growth team which focuses on conversion of free parent to paid parent.
- Discuss and work on the pain point of the user's journey and improve user funnel
- Provide parents or teachers better platform to make them pay to access new features
- Developed external and internal facing React applications alongside multiple micro-services utilizing the NestJS framework
- Working with user stories in an agile / scrum environment

▼ Full stack developer | Zenjob GmbH

Nov 2019 - Nov 2021



Zenjob is a platform which enables part-time jobbers to organize their working life freely and provides companies with motivated and flexible employees.

- Acted as a full stack JavaScript engineer for the talent acquisition team focused on users journey from Sign up to Onboarding.
- Discuss and work on the pain point of the user's journey and improve user funnel
- Ensuring our users had a pleasant and digital-first experience
- Developed external and internal facing React applications alongside multiple micro-services utilizing the NestJS framework
- Working with user stories in an agile / scrum environment

▼ Full stack developer | Digital Trons

May 2016 - Oct 2019



DigitalTrons is a service based company which offers solutions to startups, entrepreneurs, and growing businesses around the world, specialized in the software development.

- Gather the requirements from the client during weekly calls
- Architecting the project from the scratch and set the weekly goals to deliver
- Break it down the bi-weekly deliverables and delegate to the team
- Take a ownership of team's achievement and experiences
- Manage and deploy different environments of the front end and back end apps

▼ Full stack developer | Improwised Technology Pvt. Ltd

July 2015 - May 2016



Improvised also is a service based company which is working toward its goal of empowering its clients with the cutting edge solutions and proficient services..

- Get the requirements from client
- Set a weekly goals to deliverabls
- Coordinate with the team and keep the track of assigned tickets.

EDUCATION (2) -

Bachelors in Computer engineering | Atmiya Institute of Science and Technology

2011 - 2015

CGPA: 6.93

LANGUAGES

Hindi *Native speaker*

English

Fluent